

MADELINE CHAPMAN



6137 E Gateway Ct Boise, ID 83716



(208) 917 - 0543



maddi.chapman@gmail.com



www.madeline-chapman.com

ABOUT ME

Diligent and detail—oriented professional with over 3 years work experience in web design and development and over 6 years experience playing a lead role in the project life cycle in disciplines including education, social services, and technology.

I design, develop and modify new and existing responsive websites, web forms and marketing material with special attention to accessibility and UX. Clients and team members often recognize me for creating visually appealing, uncluttered sites.

EDUCATION

2014-2016 Lewis-Clark State College - B.A.S Web Development

Html 5, CSS3. Sass, Bootstrap, wireframing, working with frameworks, design principles and styles, interaction using Javascript and JQuery, development life cycle, logical operating, optimizing design for web.

2003-2007 University of Idaho - B.A Graphic Design.

Layout design, typography, digital imaging using Adobe Photoshop, color theory, pre-press and print production, package design, and information design.

EXPERIENCE

2017-2019 HomeCU, Inc. - Web Developer

Responsible for website design projects from discovery phase, through prototyping design, development, launch, and post-launch maintenance. Primary tools include HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, some JS, and Creative Suite.

2014-2016 Stemfinity, Inc. - Website and Product Management Intern

Designed and updated product landing pages. Software: OpenCart CMS, HTML, CSS, Photoshop. Designed product brochures for print. Software: InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop.

2015-2017 Lilypad, LLC - Clinical Supervisor

Responsible for case management, data recording, providing explanation of data and adaptations to plan to ensure progress. Implemented client training and collaborated with interdisciplinary team.

training and condocrated with interdisciplinary team.

2012-2015 Idaho Center for Autism - Clinical Supervisor

SKILLS

HTML5



Proficient

CSS3



Proficient

Javascript



Novice

Bootstrap



Proficient

Illustrator



Photoshop

Proficient



Novice



Proficient

ient De Proficient